/*
   Sunday, April 16, 20176:51:55 PM
   User: 
   Server: ABASIT-PC\SQLEXPRESS
   Database: womens_working
   Application: 
*/

'MAKER' table
- Unable to create index 'PK_MAKER_1'.  
The CREATE UNIQUE INDEX statement terminated because a duplicate key was found for the object name 'dbo.MAKER' and the index name 'PK_MAKER_1'. The duplicate key value is (ACC-0000).
Could not create constraint. See previous errors.
The statement has been terminated.

